For the ultimate Browns gear, head to
the Browns Pro Shop, a fanatics
experience. It's right next to
Huntington Bakefield. Jerseys, hats,
hoodies, collectibles, exclusive merch
you will not find anywhere else. Shop in
store or online at shop.cl browns.com.
The Browns Pro Shop, official merch for
true Browns fans. And now we head to the
podium where linebacker and defensive
rookie of the year Carson Sweet
>> Rookie of the Year.
>> Back with the media.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Did you know any of them?
>> Not not super well, but I mean cross
paths.
>> How you guys doing?
>> I'm doing good. Good to be back. How
different does it feel right now for you
kind of going into your first full off
season but at least you know coming off
of a season where you sort of know the
the ins and outs of
>> it's definitely a lot nicer than coming
in as a rookie and you have to basically
learn everything new and uh you know
where every place where everywhere in
the building is. I'm not getting lost
you know this time around. So, so that's
nice and it's it's just good to be
around, you know, you know all the guys,
so you come back and you're looking
forward to seeing everyone and and
getting to meet new people.
>> First time we've talked to you since
winning that defensive rookie of the
year award. Just now that that's over,
what did that mean to you and just the
whole presentation of it and having your
dad giving the
>> Yeah, that was pretty cool having uh my
whole family was there which was uh you
know cool to share that with all them
and you know just to be able to receive
that. a great honor, but you know now I
guess you know the mindset is just you
know what's next you know keep building
off of it.
>> What are your first impressions of Mike
Rutenberg and just what you kind of
think of him so far and maybe what has
his message to you been a little bit?
>> Yeah it's been great um getting to know
him. Uh a lot of energy um you know
somebody that you know I'll be talking
to every day and and working with
closely and I think um you know good
things are going to come from it. I'm
excited
>> season look like for you? uh in terms of
you know a little relaxation but also
trying to get locked in. Last year you
said you wanted this year to be even
bigger than last year. So what does it
look like for you as you enter this
phase of offseason workouts here?
>> Yeah, I think that the beginning of
offseason was just just getting healthy
and and getting the body right again. I
think the that rookie year is a long
year. You don't really get a break from,
you know, your college season to to
training to draft to to everything like
that. So, you know, really just get the
body back to healthy. And now it's um
you know, just the same thing as always,
trying to find every everything that I
can get better at and and finding ways
to do that throughout throughout this
process.
>> I know you're only two days in, but has
coach Rener talked about what's going to
change whether it's schematically,
philosophically from when uh
>> Yeah, I think every coach, you know,
comes in with with what they want um you
know, their pillars to be and and the
mindset. And I think, you know, as a
defense, we're trying to build on what
we did last year and we're still going
to, you know, schematically, we we're
we're still with the attack front and
and we're going to go get after people.
And I think that that's really the
mindset there. And um you know, as as
everyone has their, you know, own uh own
wrinkles and stuff that they'll add in.
So, I'm excited to learn those and and
really continue to build on what we did.
>> When you talk about when you talk about
getting better, I mean, it's hard to
kind of look back at last year and point
at the things that you could have done
better. So, what what are some of the
things you've kind of circled and that
you want to do better?
>> Yeah, I think there's a lot of things to
get better at, whether it's just, you
know, the preparation throughout the
throughout the week, uh, game week and
and figuring out really, you know, what
to watch, how to watch film and things
like that. But even just in this time,
whether it's, you know, improving the
the football knowledge, football
intelligence, right, or um, just finding
better ways to attack the ball and um,
really get those punch outs. I think
that's something I'm I'm really going to
work on this year. and um just
continuing to grow in terms of you know
patience behind behind the ball and and
being able to see things and and uh you
know being ready by the snap
>> as a unit Carson what can you guys do to
be better than last year?
>> Uh I think you know as a unit we got we
got great players all over the field and
I think for us if if we're all
communicating and we're all on the same
page um you know that's what you want
for a defense and you know I think us
all being on the same page knowing what
we're all doing is is big moving
forward. How do you think that you guys
as a unit have responded to the
departure of everybody loves so much?
>> Yeah, I think um the response has been
great. Obviously, you know, everyone
loves Schwarz and and um you know, we
all love playing for him, but but the
mindset's still the same. You go in and
we're finding out how we can be the best
defense we can be with um you know, the
coaches that around us, and we have
great coaches around this year, too. and
and so just looking forward to to being
able to do that
>> about um adding Quincy Williams to your
guys' group. Have you had a chance to to
get to know him much yet and how
exciting?
>> Yeah. No, I'm I'm very excited to be
able to you know have him in the room
and um you know be able to learn from
him. He's been in the league uh a long
time and so he's he's got a lot of stuff
to to teach and um just just the energy
he brings too is is something you can
already tell from two days. So it's
going to be something that that I'm
excited to to be around the whole year.
You talked about like last year
especially being such a whirlwind
training for the draft and then you get
drafted and then play a whole season.
Why this year was it so important for
you to be here as early as you are
understanding the offseason program?
Yeah, I think um you know for me I just
want to be able to to
do as much as I can and get better and I
think the the place for me to do that is
here and obviously we have all uh you
know the Rudy here and a lot of whole
new new coaches and so I think it's
important to to get to meet them as well
and um understand them and um you know
just I was excited too to be around you
know all the guys again and see them and
and be able to work with them.
How how does it feel when you walk into
a building and you see guys that are
that have been here rehabbing here? Uh
Quinton Judkins is one of those guys
working to try to get back on the field.
What does it mean as a as a teammate of
theirs to to be around them?
>> Yeah, just seeing the work that they put
into and you know, at least for me, I
was back in California, it was sunny, so
I don't know if I could have done the
cold for for that long. So just seeing,
you know, the work that they put in and
um, you know, the mindset they have to
get back, get healthy so that they can,
you know, contribute um to this team is
is is pretty special. And then just, you
know, being able to see them outside of
that and just, you know, as as boys, you
know, hang out and um just see them
again after a while. It's been good.
>> What did you take away from Todd's
opening message and uh what have you
been your early impressions?
>> Uh, I think it was great. I think um a
lot of it's just about the mindset of
this team and and how we're going to
play and and you know the goal here is
to go win a Super Bowl. I think that's
that's the end goal and that's what's
been established and you know I'm I'm
looking forward to to you know working
towards that.
>> Think I saw you were in Hawaii like for
an event that Dylan was putting on. How
did that come together and how you how
you enjoy that trip?
>> Um me and Dylan hang out a lot and you
know I'm not gonna say no to an excuse
to go to Hawaii. So, so, uh, it was
raining a lot that day, too. Um, but
just, you know, wanted to go out there
and and be able to support him and then,
you know, also take a nice four or five
days and sit in the sun.
>> The fact that you guys have all the
position coaches back on defense, how
important is that for you guys to build
on what you did last year?
>> Yeah, I think the continuity is is
extremely helpful. And, um, for me
specifically, having Tar's great. you
know, you come in, you you already have
uh you know, that connection with the
coach and um you know, you know, you
know each other and I think that's
really helpful in in you know, being
able to build.
>> What's um going through the whole
offseason program this summer? What's
important for you do you think as you
guys sort of ramp things up here? And
obviously there's
>> Yeah. Um, you know, I think for me, like
like what I talked about, it's just
finding the areas that I want to get
better, um, get better at, whether it's,
you know, things on the field, things
off the field, and, um, you know,
finding tangible ways to to measure it,
to watch it, to to to get better, and,
um, yeah, keep growing.
>> I know it's early, but what's Tar
Tarver's early message been to you about
this next season? Yeah, I think uh me
and Tarv have talked a lot about um
areas to improve and and how we're going
to do that and and what to do um to get
there and um just too excited to be back
and and be around him. Um you know, I
got to go go back to Cali more than he
did, too. So, he's he's a little jealous
of that. But, uh you know, I'm just
excited to be around him, too, and the
energy he brings.
>> Season about preparing your body to get
through a full 17 games slate. Yeah, I
think uh just the the preparation you
have for your body is important and you
know sometimes as you're playing
football things are going to happen you
can't control and it's just a matter of
you know doing everything you can to to
feel as good as you can on game day and
um you know try and do everything I can
to stay on the field.
>> Todd was mentioning that he tried to set
this program up in such a way that you
guys want to be here. Uh so what about
the program sort of is going to make it
enjoyable or fun in addition to all the
work.
>> Yeah, I think you know if if you love
football, you're going to love being
here. I think that's what it is. That's
what that's what we're doing every day
is football and and um you know, you're
you're with your brothers every day and
uh you're doing football and I think
that's that's really the base of it. If
you love football, you're going to love
this.
Coming up next on this special edition
of Cleveland Browns Daily, Z goes
one-on-one with wrestling icon Matt
Hardy. You're listening to Cleveland
Browns Daily. We are presented by Valley
Bet, official sports betting part of
your Cleveland Browns. Please bet
responsibly.
Welcome back to Cleveland Browns Daily
brought to you by Valley Beneficial
Sports Betting partner of your Cleveland
Browns. And this is folks a great
personal treat for me as we are welcomed
by one of the greatest professional
wrestlers of all time, Matt Hardy. You
know him as broken Matt Hardy, woken
Matt Hardy. Matt Hardy version one. And
of course, he is a multi-time 15
different, this is according to
cagematch.net, 15 different tag titles
held with his brother throughout his
career, multiple single titles. It's
just an honor to talk with you, an honor
to be with you and thanks so much for
taking the time today.
>> Uh thanks for having me, man. Yeah, 15
uh major ones, I think, is is what they
are counting it at right now. Uh we've
had about uh we've had four almost 50.
We've had 47 alltogether different. 47.
Well, when you go on an expedition for
gold, you're going to you're going to
collect quite a bit.
>> And we love to do it. We can't do it
enough.
>> Exactly. All right. Coming up this
Saturday right here in Cleveland, April
11th at the Woolstein Center. It's TNA
Rebellion. You and your brother Jeff
will be defending the tag team titles,
TNA tag team titles against
people who quite frankly you've had some
runins with in the past in terms of
you're looking talking Brian Meyers and
and Bear Brona, but against the system,
how much you looking forward to that
one? and then obviously walking in as
champions, but more importantly walking
out still the TNA tag team champions.
>> Uh very excited for it. I mean, uh
Cleveland is an amazing wrestling city.
Uh for people that don't know, Cleveland
is uh is where myself and Jeff, we got
put on the map. That is where
>> I was supposed to lead with that.
>> Well, that that is where the
>> October 17th, 1999, No Mercy. That's
right.
>> Yeah. 1999 No Mercy. And that that match
changed everything for us. We went from
being WWE wrestlers to WWE superstars.
That was the night. Also, it's a very
fine memory for me. I won the first ever
uh scramble match for the ECW World
Championship there in Cleveland as well.
So, Cleveland has been a good city to me
and I'm hoping it is good to me this
Saturday as we are facing a very tough
team. Brian Meyer is extremely talented.
Bear Bronson is a newcomer. He is the
wild card. He is very unknown, but he is
a very, very dangerous man. And I think
the system is more dangerous now than
they ever been.
>> And they've won they've twotime tag team
champions the system. They're different
members obviously along with Brian Myers
there. How have you and your brother
Jeff? What keeps you going? I mean, you
have what one of the great careers in
the history of this business? You've
been doing it, as I mentioned, from the
trampolines in the 80s in Cameron, North
Carolina. Start Omega. Then by 99,
you're in the WWE. And you just
mentioned it October 17th right here in
Cleveland. Changes everything. You were
the new brood then, not even the Hardy
Boys at that time. And here we are. It's
2026, brother. you go through and you
look at the body of work that you guys
have put together, not only from a
creative standpoint, but from the
physicality and what you've literally
put your bodies through. What keeps you
doing this here in the year 2026, not
only doing it, doing it at the highest
of levels. Uh I I just think more than
anything, it is our passion for pro
wrestling as children and as kids. Once
pro wrestling got a hold of us, uh, we
loved it so much and it became our dream
and we were both, uh, obsessed with
becoming pro wrestlers because we
thought it was like these guys are
living, breathing superheroes, you know,
people who are doing stuff, you're doing
it live, there's sports, there's drama,
there's entertainment, a little bit
everything. And internally, you know,
sure, we're 51 and 48, but internally we
feel like we're 21 and 18. And I think
that's what keeps us going. It it is our
passion for pro wrestling. And some
people would say it is a uncommon
passion uh as that Omega DVD said, you
know, because we have we've taken a lot
of bumps off our bump card, but I would
just say it is passion and love for the
business.
>> You have to have it, right? I mean,
there's no other way that you could do
what it is that you're doing. And I've
been lucky enough to befriend, you know,
some people in in your line of work,
Matt Cardona, Dolph Ziggler, The Miz.
Uh, and many of the same story. This was
our dream. This is something we were
hooked on as as kids, and now you get to
live it. And I will tell you this, I've
been to a lot of great wrestling events.
I've been to a lot of Wrestlemania. I've
had the opportunity to be front row for
a lot of them. In fact, when and I know
that I don't know how this match sits
with you. Historically, Wrestlemania 25,
brother versus brother. I was there in
second row when Jeff hits Swanon throws
his shirt in the crowd. That's in my
house, his his tank. So, you guys have
had so many big moments, but I like I
said, I've been to a lot when you guys
came back and I want to say it's
Wrestlemania 33. Is that Did I get that
right? Orlando, Florida. Yes.
>> So, your tag title match was going to be
it was the latter match of surprise.
Obviously, you guys come back. The next
match was going to be Miz Shane McMahon
and I was there with with the Miz and so
we got brought down. We're down like on
the going to be ready to be moved into
the front on the camera side for his
match.
>> We obviously nobody had any idea when
your guys music hit and we're walking.
We're on the floor now of the arena of
the stadium, the football stadium down
there in Orlando, the Citrus Bowl.
>> It shook. The ground shook. Was that one
of, from your standpoint, one of the
greatest pops that you've ever been a
part? I think it's one of the greatest
pops in the history of wrestling,
period. But what was that moment like
for you guys through your eyes?
>> Absolutely. I mean, it it was so wild
because Jeff and I, there was so much
secrecy around that, right? They did a
really good job of uh of not letting
that secret out. There were less than 10
people that really knew we were going to
be there, that we were ressigned and
everything else. And uh and we played
our part. We did everything that we
could to uh to keep things on the DL.
>> Yes, you did.
>> And uh and and we got there about an
hour before they ask us to get hoodies
in Orlando in April, which was kind of
challenging. They ended up being pink
hoodies. If you ever seen the
documentary, that's pretty cool. Uh so
we sneak into the building. We get onto
a bus. Uh we talk to the other couple
teams for just a few minutes about uh
the game plan of what we got going on.
And then once the first entrance goes
down and goes to the ring, they say go.
And then we ran from that bus and
gorilla was up three flights of stairs.
It was three stairs. My wife was
pregnant. She was carrying our
one-year-old, one and a halfyear-old on
her back. So she was furious at me,
cursing me out in Spanish.
Uh, we got up there and then immediately
it was just so overwhelming because
there was, you know, John Cena and Shawn
Michaels and Triple H and Ms. McMahon
and everybody else and it's like this
big family reunion and then all of a
sudden the music is hitting and we're
going and when we're walking out, we
have no idea what this venue looks like.
We hadn't seen it yet. We had done an
autograph signing for six hours that day
and
>> Oh, I remember that was the distraction.
Yeah.
>> Yeah, that that was a distraction. And I
I taken a photo when our whole family,
House Hardy, flew in that I was going to
post saying, "Thank you for the weekend.
It was great." And I did post that
saying that we had already left.
>> And uh and then and then we walked out
and the crowd was so legitimately su uh
excited. And the thing that was so
surprising to me is that, you know, TNA
was a company that was on the verge of
going out of business and the the Broken
Universe stuff. Broken Mountain Brother
Nero made it hot and we get we was sold
to Anthem, a new company actually took
over and and it gave us a lifeline to a
degree and so many people, you know,
said, "Oh, TNA's dying." But, you know,
the whole delete delete delete. There
were
>> We're going to get there. I have many
questions. Don't worry. We're going to
get there.
>> There were there were 50,000 people
doing that in Wrestlemania and they were
just as emotionally uh excited as they
could possibly be. And and for us, it
was just exhilarating. It was
intoxicating. it. Usually in those
moments, you're just so overwhelmed and
it but this felt like a dream. It felt
surreal. It feels like it's blurry
around the edges as I'm trying to, you
know, recall the the the memory because
it was just such an amazing moment. And
and and the the energy was palpable in
that. And I I think the further we get
away from that moment, the the higher
and higher it claims, uh higher and
higher it climbs as one of the greatest
moments in Hardy Boy history.
>> I think it's one of the greatest moments
in wrestling history. And I'm not I'm
not being facitious. I mean, I've been I
was at every Wrestlemania from 19
through and had, you know, fortunately
to be in good spot from 19 through I
missed 18, which would have been Hogan
Rock, which probably would be the one
thing that I think maybe be on a par,
but from 19 through 40.
>> Well, the first match you saw at
Wrestlemania was me versus Rey Mysterio.
>> V1
Steve Koffield. Absolutely. I remember
that. Absolutely. Shannon Moore, the the
Matitude follower. You do you still
detest green beans and and mustard?
Well, mustard. It just strongly disliked
the test. Powerful word.
>> It is.
>> Mad fact. Matt is undefeated as a
singles competitor in Wrestlemania.
>> Undertaker can't say that.
>> All right.
>> No, he can't. Not anymore.
>> I'm two and0, baby. I got the streak
when it comes to singles matches
>> about going back real quick to that man.
When you come out, are you Did Kofi
know?
>> Yes. The
>> Okay. Cuz their reaction was off the
charts. But but those guys, Kofi and
those guys, they only knew they they
smartened them up like 20 minutes
before.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> They knew they were going to be
announcers, but they were like, whoa. I
mean, they were it was still it was
still I feel like they had they had they
haven't seen us.
>> Uh and and it was going to be a shocker
and surprise. So that their their
emotion and their reactions were very
authentic and and once again kudo uh
kudos to Kofi and uh Big E and Xavier
because they they really they help make
that moment even more special with their
reactions.
>> Well, I think there's something special
about what one of the cool things about
the business that you're in and and the
fraternity that you're in that you know,
like I said, I've been able to observe
adjacently is like when you have that's
respect. That is the ultimate respect.
when you get guys out there marking out
for for you like that's the ultimate
sign of respect and I think that's so
cool and you guys have been so
influential like Kofi Kingston there's
no doubt you guys influence Kofi
Kingston's career life trajectory all of
it you know that's to me that's what
that's what makes it right those are
kind of moments you live for sure it is
and and sometimes you know people go
like do you guys ever look back and
think about how influential you are and
like we we talk now at at ComicCons and
appearances we do to so many fathers or
mothers and their children that are like
now both fans of the Hardies and and
they support the Hardy Boys and they
they're catching up on, you know, all of
our matches and our body of work and and
it's amazing. They like bond over it and
and the fact that we have become
generational talents. The fact that we
have worked with so many young tag teams
that said we you were my favorite tag
team. You inspired me to do this. I
wanted to do this because I saw you and
Jeff doing it and and we get to work
with them now. So, it's it's real cool,
man. I don't even think we we we don't
take the time to like look back, stop
and look back and go like we did all
this influentially. Uh because we we
still want to be living in the moment.
We want to be present in the moment and
still be as good as we can be every
single night. Uh and that's what we want
to do this weekend against the system
obviously.
>> Yeah. And you're going to keep those tag
titles. And one of the things that's
cool about this kind of TNA run that
you've been on is you mentioned, you
know, the ladder match obviously that
was with Edge and Christian. Then we go
back to obviously Wrestlemania 17, we
think about TLC 2 when that involved the
Dudley Boys. for you guys to get to have
that kind of, you know, that's what's
one of the beautiful things about
wrestling is that sometimes you get an
opportunity to to close a book but have
the proper book in to get that match
with the Dudley's. It was for me
>> poetry, perfect cinema, everything you
could have wanted out of that for you
guys. What was that like to to to lock
up one more time with them? I
>> I mean it it was amazing. I am so so
proud of that match. Um, Devon had had
some very serious health issues and he
he worked extremely hard to overcome
them and get into the to the best shape
he could. He he worked hard to get
cleared and he did get cleared and you
know we went into that we went into that
match with two missions. One to have an
amazing match and show people that we
can still make magic happen together.
Totally. and and we did that and and the
other mission was to keep Devon safe and
healthy and and give him one last great
match to really book in his career much
like you said before and uh we are so
proud of that match. I I I just watched
that match back yesterday actually
because they just recently released the
video. They put the full match out on
the TNA YouTube channel and if you
haven't seen it yet, go watch it. It's
great.
>> Do it. Yes, I urge everyone. We did
enough uh exciting crazy table hotspots
to make people think like wow this is
like them in 2000 but we did great
storytelling as well talking about like
you know the Dudley's Bubba is looking
at the very end like okay well it's over
for us now it's over for me it's over
for us and and the thing that is super
surprising about that match nor Jeff nor
I we knew that was going to be Devon's
last match we want to get him through it
we did not know that they were both
going to retire and on top of that the
boots at the end of the match that was
an absolutely authentic moment
uh whenever you saw that happening, that
was our emotion uh in real time because
we had no idea that was happening.
>> That's so cool. And you know, one of the
things that's amazing about it is it's
one thing to like, you know, to lay that
out to be like, okay, we're going to do
this and you didn't know they were going
to try at the end, but say, you know,
we're going to go one more time, but
then to actually be able to get through
and what you brought to light about
Devon to get through it and execute it.
Like that's the that's the beauty of it
is that you guys had this vision and
then delivered it it sounds like against
some odds and that's the be that's the
beauty of pro wrestling. That's the
absolute beauty of what you can do.
>> I mean that that that is the beauty of
that is the beauty of the art of pro
wrestling, you know, because we do
control uh several different aspects of
the industry and and and there are ways
you can make things that seem impossible
happen. And that is that is beautiful.
That's a beautiful thing about pro
wrestling.
>> There's no doubt about it. I I I went to
get back this earlier, but you mentioned
the broken universe. So, I have a group
of friends that we've all watched
wrestling for forever.
We could not have been bigger fans of
the Broke universe. I remember when you
went on Jericho's podcast, you did a
talk as Jericho that was like two hours
where you went through the whole thing.
I was riveted. One year I was driving to
the NFL scouting combine, which is from
Cleveland to India. It's about a four
and a half hour drive. I listened to it
there and back. That's how much I
enjoyed the podcast and the broken
universe and you know Scarsgard and
Vanguard one and just everything every
detail. How where in the world okay for
people who maybe don't know about it and
you should go see 2016 I want to say if
I if I have that right I think it's in
that in that era
to reinvent yourself that way it's kind
of you think of the great you know icons
whether Madonna you know just to
completely reinvent yourself and you
could had to have the most fun ever
doing it but how did you kind of work
that out? How do you workshop the
accent, which I think makes it on some
level, and just have that unbelievable
renaissance to your career?
>> Uh, well, the funny thing is I I've
always tried to keep my finger on the
pulse of pro wrestling, like where
what's going on? And and and we're at
that point where
>> the wrestlers are getting smaller, their
height's getting a little shorter, they
don't weigh quite as much, wrestling is
kind of changing, and and and matches
are more exciting. there's much more uh
acrobatics in it, you know, and we we
ushered some of that in obviously back
in the day when we first started doing
our things, you know. So, I was like,
well, this is what pro wrestling is and
where it's at right now. And work rate
is very high. These guys have to have
great matches. That's kind of like a
requirement. If you're having a match on
top of telling a story, you have to have
make it really action-packed and it has
to be good quality action. I was like,
what if I go in the opposite direction
of that and I try something that is a
throwback to the early 90s, Papa Shango
or when Undertaker first started and he
was magical. What if I tried to create
this supernatural character that was
very unique and my wife and I we had uh
start we had binged True Blood over a
few and I I thought the whole vampire
concept was so cool how you see Eric
Northman who was my favorite on there.
uh he had lived for a thousand years and
you see all these different periods and
how his clothing changes and how his
hairstyles changed and everything else
and it's like it would be so great if
you could portray some sort of character
like that. Obviously I can't be immortal
but what if I could say I am cognizant
of where my soul and my body has been.
So then that's when the body became the
vessel the vessel became my essence and
uh the the fact that you listened to
that talk as Jericho interview that is
delightful you know that you listen to
it over four hours
>> wonderful
>> I I I tried to look I tried to look for
words that were very uh archaic and p
and I tried to incorporate those you
know that way I could seem like I am a
soul that was from thousands of years
ago and that was kind of the whole
concept behind the brokenhe hearty
persona. Did you have any idea that it
was going to become the phenomenon that
it become? As you mentioned, and we fast
forward, you know, kind of jumping
around, but to that wrestling, a
football stadium is chanting delete. You
had not been on WWE TV in years,
>> right? And and the broken universe is
what brought us back to WWE
>> 100%. It was the hottest thing in
wrestling.
>> You know, Vince Vince said, "Why why are
people doing that? Why why are FANS
DOING DELETE, DELETE, DELETE? WHAT IS
THAT?" And you know, someone said,
"Well, that's what the Hardies are
doing. the Hardies. They're, you know,
they they have these new broken
characters and and it's very popular,
very hot right now. And it's viral
online. He said, "Bring them back. Bring
them all back." There's only two of us,
fans. So,
>> that's what when you go into the lake of
reincarnation. I mean, you never know
what's going to happen, right? There are
there are more versions. You're right
about that. But it's it's crazy how the
Hardy compound became such a character
in the Broken Universe, you know, which
so beloved
>> and family, right? Senor Benjamin was
your father-in-law.
>> No doubt. Everybody. Yeah. And you know,
Scarsgard, people love Scarsgard.
Vanguard.
>> Scarsgard's the best.
>> When when Vanguard won when Vanguard one
uh got hurt and killed, like people were
so sympathetic.
>> I didn't I like it. Yeah,
>> it was wild. Yeah. Um but man, it it was
it was the most fun. That year of doing
Broken Mount was the most fun I've ever
had in my entire career. And and just
the the the fact that I got to create
and think out of the box and do stuff
that was so different was so much fun.
And I'm so proud of it. It was so cool
that we got to do a little bit of it uh
last year at NXT because we did a really
cool deal where Jeff and I got beat up.
We dipped into the lake of reincarnation
and did a big video, came back as Broken
Matt and Brother Nero. Thursday night on
Impact, you're going to see a brutal
>> tag team table match uh between, you
know, ourselves and the Righteous. And
and I think I figured out finally what
the Righteous's gold was. I I think
their goal is to bring out Broken Matt
and Brother Nero. And I don't know, they
>> Be careful what you ask for. Yeah, be
very careful what you ask for because
that that that could be a decision they
are going to extremely regret. So, uh we
we're going to be battered and beat up
going into the ring with the system, but
we are the Hardies. You know, we uh uh a
new catchphrase that I just said and and
and Tommy Dreamer was a big fan of it.
You know, uh there's no one that has
hardyh hardy heart because regardless of
how bad you beat us down, you know, we
will not die. We have the guts to just
keep ticking, man.
>> I like that. I'm not going to repeat it,
but I like what you're saying right
there. Again, this is all going down
here in Cleveland. I mean, you get an
opportunity to see Living Legends still
at the top of their game, the Hardy Boys
against the system. TNA tag team titles
on the line. TNA Rebellion, Saturday,
April the 11th, 2026 at the Woolstein
Center. Tickets are on sale right now
through Ticketmaster. And Matt, I just I
want to leave you with this because I
could talk to you all day and I know you
are a very busy man. You got a lot going
on, but this is a great thrill for me.
I'll tell you this kind of leave you
when you talk about kind of the impact
you have. So my kids for a long time I
had my kids like pretty hard into
wrestling. Now they're in high school
and you know they've moved on to to
other things but we went to a bunch of
Royal Rumbles, Wrestlemania together. My
son had like all the figures, play all
the video games and everything.
>> There are four people four people and I
told them that I was doing this
interview and they both marked out huge.
They're like you're going to talk to the
Hardies. You're going to talk to Mad
Hardy. So you, Jeff, AJ Styles, and
Kofi, who was always so nice to them
when he they got a chance to meet him
backstage. Those are the four people
that they to this day like when that's
wrestling to them. The Hardy Boys, AJ
Styles and Kofi Kingston.
>> Outstand. A AJ and Kofi are both amazing
humans. Very good. Great, great, great,
great pick by your kids.
>> Yeah. Yeah. We're raising them right.
Raising them right. Exactly.
>> Well, Matt, thank you so much for the
time. Tear it up at Rebellion. Get
through that table match with these no
good doers. We don't like these people,
but if they get Brother Nero and Broken
Madbag, they're going to get what they
uh had what they had coming. But go
check them out. TNA Rebellion, Saturday,
April 11th, 2026, Woline Center again,
and get your tickets at Ticket Master.
Mahari, I got to tell you, a personal
great thrill for me today. I really
appreciate the time and the
conversation.
>> Thank you. And I hope to see each and
every one of you in Cleveland. If not, I
may have to delete you.
It's perfect. We'll be back. More Browns
Daily right after this.
Welcome back in to Cleveland the Browns
daily. We're presented by Valley Bet,
official sports betting partner. If you
Cleveland the Browns, please bet
responsibly. We're going to have a
little fun here on a Friday edition of
the program. Celebrity golf forsesome
for Augusta and the Masters. So the idea
here, Gibbe, is we are playing in this
foresome. Yes. Um, now there is one
issue with your parameters that I've
found and I'm not sure if this is you
and Gman or
>> I think I know where you're going.
>> Significant issue.
>> It's a relatively significant issue
>> and that is that one of your selection
criteria, two of them are make perfect
sense. One golfer singledigit handicap,
one golfer with a handicap between 10
and 20. But then you also have one
golfer with a handicap that is 21 or
higher. With this AC with this segment,
you have given us a list of golfers that
we can choose from, which is a fantastic
list. Over a hundred golfers we can
choose from. And these are their actual
handicaps.
>> Correct.
>> The only problem we have here is
>> 20. 20 should have been included in the
third run.
>> I think I I
>> And I was busy because we were taping
other people.
>> So, let's go to 20. Let's hold on.
>> I think that's going to really open it
up.
>> It doesn't really open it up all that
much. I've I've done the research here
and I think what we're looking for I
think we want a zero to nine,
a 10 to 17 and then an 18 plus.
If you're if you're trying to get like
three
>> 10 to 17
>> reasonably equalized buckets, the last
one's got to be 18 plus.
>> I'm I'm cool with that. I'm cool with 10
to 17.
>> Great. I I appreciate the effort.
>> 18's a bogey golfer.
>> 18 and there's
>> We get
>> You would know that. you would have a
better idea of that than I would.
>> We throw in a few more that way.
>> All right. Um, should we do this draft?
Let me ask you guys this. If you were
like I if this were us playing because
this is us playing with the foresome.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Um, so should we do this draft
style? And I'm just going to I mean I
assume we're all just going to do it
with the guy that we would most like to
play with.
>> Have the most fun.
>> I think we should do it. I think you
should Everybody should write down if
they had their brothers. Yeah.
>> What their ideal team was.
>> Okay. But then and we'll reveal that at
the end. But I do think we should do a
draft. And Gibby, are you participating?
Is Young Is Young Gabriel participating?
>> I think Gabriel's tied up. He's got some
things going on.
>> Dr. J.
>> Dr. J. The golf is not Dr. Jay's strong.
>> So So the three of us will do a draft.
>> The three of us will do a snake draft.
And but also write down your ideal that
if you were left completely unfettered
what your what your team would be.
>> Okay, let me just tell you this right
now. I think I have a dream team. I
can't
>> Are there some people fudging their
handicaps?
>> Any scenario any scenario
where my close personal friend Mr. Dog
is an 18?
>> Don't worry about that.
>> That's what it says. I can't see a
scenario
where that's the case.
>> Don't worry about that.
>> Pay very little attention to this. Who
on this list is there's some real
surprises.
For example, like I would be very
interested in watching Charlies Theren
move around a place at and shoot 82.
Like to see that.
>> How about Alba? You got a pretty
>> Alba's a Well, she's an 18, but
Katherine Bell's a two.
>> Katherine Bell's a two. She's a two.
She's a stick dog.
>> All right.
>> Yeah. A fun little list.
>> This is a fun list. The uh
>> Who is a two?
>> Kristen Bell.
>> Katherine Bell.
>> Was that?
>> She was um she was in Bruce Almighty.
>> No idea.
>> She was in um one of those CBS
procedurals like NCIS Annapolis or
something.
>> I like the idea of of Shakira at a 20 or
at an 18.
>> Yeah, those both win.
All right, I'm ready. I'm prepared. I
mean, they're two. I mean, I Yeah, I'm
good. I'm good. What are we going to do
with LD with the double handicap? What
do I make of that?
>> It just means he's a 13.6.
>> Oh, 6. Oh, he's got it. He's dialed in
then.
>> He's 13.
>> He knows exactly what he is.
>> Yeah, the those are, interestingly, he,
Ker, and Murray. There's some people
have real like when you got a a point,
that's that's much more of a you know,
that's a real handicap.
>> That's a real one. That's a real one.
Um, all right. So, how do we want to do
the draft order?
>> Should we have Dr. Jay pick the draft
order?
>> Go ahead, Dr. J. Snake draft. Go ahead.
>> Or wait, you went last in the Masters.
>> He went last.
>> I went last.
>> You went last.
>> I was middle. I was even. Stephen.
>> All right. So, go Gibbe. I'll go last.
>> All right. We're good. Dr. J.
>> All right. So, Gibbe's going first.
>> Yep.
All right.
>> There's a lot going on here. There is
>> I hope to get two of my three. I don't
think that there's any way that I can
get all three of my three. That'd be an
impossibility.
>> I mean, I assume are we is this for
competition to have a competition?
Nobody's going to play. There's no There
is no competition.
>> Yeah. I think it's fun. Who do you want
to hang with?
>> Yeah.
>> What would be If you could pick out of
these people, who would you want to hang
with that you've laid out for us? Give
>> All right.
>> Look at Will Scarlet just shephering
people around.
>> He really is. He's a leader of men
taking people in and around.
>> There you go.
>> I look forward to you uh taking him to
watch South Carolina be Clemson.
>> Yes, that'll be fun.
>> That'll be fun.
>> Gibb, you got one?
>> Yeah. So, can I pick
>> with the number one pick?
>> Can I pick any of these?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> You can pick anybody you want. You're
picking first.
>> I'm uh I'm going McConna at 36.
>> Wow. McConna
>> with a 14 handicap. Well, that's what we
need. Why? Why you say add 36? Because
he's just listed as the 36th person.
>> Number 36 on this list.
>> He's a 14. So,
>> well, that way you can find him.
>> Yeah. Because I try to do this the way
that I do.
>> Um, you're and I first pick would be the
same person on this list. No, no. I'm
going to show you what friendship is and
I'm going to show you generosity.
>> And so, I'm going to take Bill Murray
here. I will take Bill Murray.
>> I mean,
>> he would have been your second pick. I
believe your first would have been LD.
My first would have been LD. So, I will
take Murray. Okay.
>> As my one.
>> So, then I'm going to come back and I'm
going to hit with LD. Duh. And then I'm
going to hit with Snoop. LD and Snoop
together.
>> That's a lot of fun.
>> It feels like we're gonna have a great
time. Now, I need to find
>> Now, L is LD. LD is your
>> He's my 10 to 17 and Snoop's my 18.
>> So, he's your
>> So, now I need to find a single digit
that I really want to spend some time
with.
>> Snoop. Okay. Um
All right. So, I got Murray. So, now I
want to think about who who would
operate in a fun world with Murray, who
doesn't take themselves too seriously,
might have a little bit of fun. Um,
I keep being drawn to someone that I
know neither one of you guys would would
pick. Oh, I can't have him because
Murray's a single. Murray's a single, so
I don't think it matters.
>> Oh, no.
>> I can't have him. two guys that I think
would be a great time on this, but I
can't because
>> I mean, dude, you could I think there's
a pretty good second place in the 10 to
14 category that is pretty strong. Like
quite strong.
>> I mean, I'm going through this. I'm
trying to There's three of them.
>> It's 10 to 17, right? 10 to 17. There's
three on page 21 to 44.
>> There are three
10 to 17s that are electric factories
for different reasons, but would I think
all be tremendous. my one man's opinion.
I'm gonna go um
I'm gonna go Frell. Yeah, Will Frell.
You got Will Frell and Bill Murray. Do
they I just wonder do they get along? I
hope they get along. I I was a little
red flagged on Frell because of what
happened between him and Adam McKay.
Like how they doesn't talk. They were
the longest friends and they don't talk
anymore. Like maybe Frell sucks.
>> I think it's
>> You think it's the other way? Yeah.
Okay. All right. The other one the one
that I was well I'll you guys won't pick
it so I say it the one that the one that
I think would be good and I've heard is
like the coolest dude and we would have
one thing in common which would lead to
kind of some fun conversation is Michael
Keaton.
>> So Katon is
>> like the reput he lives in Livingston,
Montana and one of his reputations is
he's past giving any about anything.
Yep.
>> So he's just his own human. Um so I I
considered him a lot. Uh I also
considered Hanks but I'll go uh I'll go
Frell. Well, I think and you also on
that same page and Gibby's already done
that one so he can't pick him. But you
got Jack Nicholson might be a fun guy to
spend.
>> What would that be like? He's got to be
in his 80s. Like does he
>> And then the Great Sand.
>> The Great Sand. Oh, he was on there. I
didn't see
>> 16.
>> Oh, there he is. The Great Sand.
>> Great Sand.
>> Sand would be a great one with LD. I
think they they're probably a very nice
operation.
>> I know. Too bad they live in the same
handicap.
>> Same handicap world. All right. Go
ahead, Gibbe. You got two picks.
I I think I want for my for for the
single.
>> You get two here. You get you get
>> you get two, buddy. Two picks back to
back.
>> You went Murray and Frell. I mean,
that's pretty
>> that's a that's incredible.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm I'm going a little I'm going Darius
Rucker.
>> He's fun.
>> He's a seven. I've hung out with him.
Good dude.
back in the uh in the Hoodie and the
Blowfish days
>> when he uh when he joined the Buckeye
Cruise for Cancer, he said, "I'll do it.
All I want to do is play golf with Urban
at Ocean Club in the Bahamas and I'm
in." And so they did that. They set it
up. Urban said, "I'd love to." So they
played Ocean Club and he came on the
Buckeye Cruise for Cancer and sang.
>> Did like six songs, took pictures.
>> That's all you need.
>> Great dude. Great dude.
incredible rendition of Purple Rain
>> out of Darius Rucker, which I would not
have guessed,
>> but crushed Purple Rain.
>> Doesn't surprise me at all.
>> All right.
>> One of his best covers is Mustang Sally.
>> Oh, yeah. Mustang.
>> What movie was that from? The
>> Mustang Sally. It's about a band in
Europe, in England, I want to say, and
that was their main song.
>> Was that I don't know.
>> Mustang Sally.
>> That's a good song. So, the the one guy
I'd like and I can't because I have MCC
at 14.
>> Yeah.
>> Like Jason Baitman I think could be a
really good
>> I think he'd be fun afternoon on the
links.
>> I think you have a good time with him.
>> I caught up. I watched a couple
episodes. I'm not all the way caught up,
but I watched two episodes of your uh
the show that you wanted me to watch.
>> The commitments. Oh,
>> I watched a couple more episodes
>> and
>> there's a lot going on. Isn't it good
though how you like they make you think
you're like oh it's definitely
>> I don't want to get too far into it
because I'm not all the way caught up
yet but I
>> we're in the same spot. We watched four
>> I believe so
>> then we're in the same spot if you watch
four. I've watched four.
>> I think I've watched four
>> but like they make it one episode you're
like oh it's definitely this and then
you see the episode through a completely
different paradigm
definitely this.
>> It's a smart show
>> and my guess is it's going to end up
being ultimately
>> something else.
>> Yeah. Neither of those from the
commitments was the movie I was looking
for. The commitments 1991 film The
Commitments. Um, all right. So, who are
your who are your bails.5 handic?
>> So, part of me really wants to take Sir
Charles.
>> Yeah.
>> So, why not?
>> I I would No, I'm gonna go a different
direction on this.
>> Where the heck?
>> Well, then there I would say that
there's more of you that doesn't.
>> Are you thinking Sly Stallone?
>> No, no, no. I've got to be
>> Are you thinking Madonna? So, him and
Are you thinking Shakira? Shakira. I
actually got to go to Madonna's
soundcheck at the Grammys in 2001 and I
hung out with Guy Richie and John
Stewart and we went to a bar and got
>> well
>> blasted in the middle of the
>> afternoon. We know that. I would also
say that as an 18 Conan O'Brien I think
>> that's where that's where I was going. I
will take Conan O'Brien.
>> That's a good group.
>> I'm gonna go Chuck.
>> I mean your group is electric. So, I've
got LD and Snoop. So,
I want I'd like I'd like you your help
with this.
>> Yep. I'm willing willing and able.
>> I have a couple ways that I'm
considering going right now.
>> Okay.
>> So, I need my single digit my
single-digit guy right now.
>> Okay.
>> And on the first page, there are a lot
of people, you know, Matt Damon. I'm
consideration for Matt Damon. Put him
>> I'm sure it'd be a good time.
>> We're going to put him in consideration.
>> All right. So, Damon's in the mix.
>> Damon's in consideration. Marky Mark is
in consideration. I don't think you want
Wahberg.
>> I'm just He's in consideration. I'm just
saying too intense.
>> He's way too intense. Like he's up at
2:45 in the morning. He's sprinting.
He's doing sprint golf. Haven't you
heard this? Like he sprints to the golf
ball. Then he's out.
>> You can't have that with soup and LD.
Although
>> LD like making fun of him might be an
electric factory. Yeah.
>> All right. I'm going to also in
consideration we're going to put Samuel
L. Jackson.
>> I like that.
>> I think that could be a lot of fun. Yep.
>> Got about two minutes, gentlemen. Here's
a little bit of a a wild card that maybe
you didn't see coming, but perhaps you
should have.
>> Katherine Zeta Jones is in serious
consideration right now.
>> She is an eight.
>> In serious consideration.
>> I used to have a massive crush on her.
Who didn't? Yeah. Masar.
>> So I could be hanging out with Katherine
Zeta Jones.
>> How great is Snoop and LVED.
>> She's unbelievable.
>> Yeah. So she's
>> she's an eight. She's that's a pretty
strong consideration there. Um and then
uh Pton Manning. Manning would be
consideration
and he's self-deprecating. Plus, he's a
really good golfer. Yeah. So, like you
could my guess is like
>> you versus him. You're you versus him, I
would take you, but I think you versus
him would be a hell of a match.
>> And he would have the knowledge of
Augusta as a member that you wouldn't.
>> Yeah.
>> Which is worth some strokes.
>> Agreed.
>> So, he's a 3.5 handicap.
>> I found an issue. An issue has been
brought to light.
Read for me the name of number two on
our list. Bo Bishop.
>> Yeah, I'll read it.
>> And Gibbe, I'd like you to read the name
of number 77 on our list.
>> Alice Cooper.
>> Give
>> Alice Cooper is also number 77.
>> He's on the list twice. He's at least
it's he's a two in both instances.
>> And then by the way, number 26 on the
list.
>> Him showing up in Wayne's world is
pretty great. He's so good.
>> Miller.
>> Milly. Number 26 on the list. Samuel L.
Jackson. Number 83 on the list,
>> Sam Jackson.
>> Samuel L. Jackson.
>> All right. Where are you going?
>> So,
>> we got like a minute left.
>> Who are you in? Who are you in? What are
your options?
>> You had Damon. I'm crowd. Damon's out.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Sam Jackson, Zeta Jones, or Payton.
>> I think you do Payton.
>> Yeah,
>> because then you have the fun with Snoop
and LD.
>> We could have a real golf, me and him.
>> LD will have a blast like talking sports
with Payton, talking NFL.
>> Yeah, there it is.
>> You get a window. He's a great time
>> and I'd be able
>> You don't have that crud Eli bringing
him down.
>> I'd be able to have a video where maybe
he narrates one of my golf shots.
>> Now you're talking. Now you're talking.
>> Zeta Joe. So can she be I'd like her to
accompany us.
>> She's got an eight. I mean that'd be
fun.
>> Yeah,
>> that'd be a scene, brother. All right.
Good stuff. Good stuff. Uh we are back
Monday, kids.
>> That's where we're at.
>> That's it.
>> We're back. We're back on a Monday.
Enjoy your weekend, everybody. Cleveland
Browns Daily presented by Valley Bet,
official sports betting partner.
Cleveland Browns. Please bet
responsibly.